const videoGames = {
    results: [
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "In what year was Hearthstone released?",
        correct_answer: "2014",
        incorrect_answers: ["2011", "2013", "2012"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "Which Nintendo 64 game did NOT have Luigi in it?",
        correct_answer: "Super Mario 64",
        incorrect_answers: ["Mario Party 2", "Paper Mario", "Super Smash Bros."],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "Which of these is a type of monster found in Minecraft?",
        correct_answer: "Skeleton",
        incorrect_answers: ["Werewolf", "Vampire", "Minotaur"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "What&#039;s the name of the main protagonist in the &quot;Legend of Zelda&quot; franchise?",
        correct_answer: "Link",
        incorrect_answers: ["Mario", "Zelda", "Pit"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "In &quot;Yo! Noid 2,&quot; The Noid can perform what special move?",
        correct_answer: "Dab",
        incorrect_answers: ["Pizza Throw", "Dodge Roll", "Spin Dash"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "Sean Bean voices the character of &quot;Martin Septim&quot; in which Elder Scrolls game?",
        correct_answer: "The Elder Scrolls IV: Oblivion",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim",
          "The Elder Scrolls III: Morrowind ",
          "The Elder Scrolls Online",
        ],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "Which one of these games wasn&#039;t released in 2016?",
        correct_answer: "Metal Gear Solid V",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Tom Clancy&#039;s The Division",
          "Killing Floor 2",
          "Hitman",
        ],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "Psych-Horror &quot;Eternal Darkness: Sanity&#039;s Requiem&quot;, developed by Silicon Knights in 2002, was published by who and on what platform?",
        correct_answer: "Nintendo&reg; Co. Ltd. | GameCube&trade;",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Sony&reg; Computer Entertainment&trade; Inc. | PlayStation&reg; 2",
          "Microsoft&reg; Game Studios&trade; | XBox&trade;",
          "Sega&reg; Enterprises Co. Ltd. | Dreamcast&trade;",
        ],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "When was &quot;Garry&#039;s Mod&quot; released?",
        correct_answer: "December 24, 2004",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "November 13, 2004",
          "December 13, 2004",
          "November 12, 2004",
        ],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "When was the video game &quot;P.A.M.E.L.A.&quot; released on Steam?",
        correct_answer: "March 9, 2017",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "January 7, 2007",
          "October 23, 1997",
          "February 16, 2015",
        ],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "Which game was exclusive to Dreamcast?",
        correct_answer: "Pen Pen TriIcelon",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Sylvester &amp; Tweety in Cagey Capers",
          "Perfect Dark",
          "Tetrisphere",
        ],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "In the original &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, what is the acceleration of Mario if he was in free fall?",
        correct_answer: "91.28 m/s^2",
        incorrect_answers: ["110  m/s^2", "9.42  m/s^2", "4.4  m/s^2"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question: "In the National Pokedex what number is Porygon-Z?",
        correct_answer: "474",
        incorrect_answers: ["376", "432", "589"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "Which of these Generation 1 Pokemon did NOT have an evolution in Generation 4?",
        correct_answer: "Jynx",
        incorrect_answers: ["Electabuzz", "Magmar", "Rhydon"],
      },
      {
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
        question:
          "In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, which map&#039;s opening cutscene shows &quot;Richtofen&quot; killing another version of himself?",
        correct_answer: "The Giant",
        incorrect_answers: ["Shadows Of Evil", "Der Eisendrache", "Moon"],
      },
    ],
  };

export{videoGames}